lecroupier.com 2009-02-24

# Le Croupier - Privacy Policy

Privacy policy

1\. This Website is operated by Barrier Interactive Gaming (“the Company”). The aim of this policy is to tell you how we will use any personal data you provide through this Website. Please read it carefully before you provide us with any personal data. 

2\. We collect the following personal data from you in order that you may register and to use this Website and our Games: your name, title, date of birth and your contact details including the country where you live and your email address.

3\. We will also ask for your payment details but these will be held by our third party payment providers. We do not have access to your payment details. 

4\. We use your personal information to invite you to join our Website and play our Games. Where you have asked to receive information from us we will use your personal information to send you newsletters or other information about us.

5\. We may share your personal data with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

6\. We may disclose your personal information to third parties:   
(i) in the event that we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect our rights or property (this includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of verification, fraud protection and credit risk reduction)   
(ii) for marketing purposes where you have indicated on your registration form that you would like to receive information from our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates about their products and services.

7\. We may also employ the services of a third party to help us provide our online services. In some cases the third party may receive your information. However, at all times, we will control and be responsible for the use of your information. 8\. We may use aggregated information for the purposes of tracking Website usage of the Web site and in order to help us improve our Website and for research and analysis purposes. We may pass this information to third parties. The aggregate information and statistics will not, however, include details that can be used to identify you.

9\. We may not transfer some of your information outside Europe, unless such transfer is required in order to manage your registration and to provide our services. Some of these countries may not have equivalent data protection legislation protecting the use of your personal information. By submitting your personal information to this Website, you consent to such transfers taking place. 

10\. When you visit our Website we send you a cookie. A cookie is a “text-only” string of information that a Website transfers to the cookie file of your computer’s hard disk so that the Website can remember who you are. Cookies may be used to help us recognise you when you return to our Website. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our Website if cookies are disabled. Find out more about cookies and how to disable/enable cookies by looking at www.allaboutcookies.org 

11\. Our Website may from time to time contain links to other web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for privacy policies or practices of other Websites to which you choose to link from this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

12\. You are entitled to see the information held about you. If you wish to do this, please contact us at through the webform on www.LeCroupier.com .We may require you to provide verification of your identity and to pay a small administration fee to provide a copy of the information we hold. Please note that in certain circumstances we may withhold access to your information where we have the right to do so under current data protection legislation.

13\. You may review, correct, update or change your personal information at any time by contacting us through the webform on www.LeCroupier.com If you opted to receive newsletters, other communications from us or third parties at the time you registered on this Website but subsequently change your mind, you may opt-out by contacting us through the webform on www.LeCroupier.com 

14\. We have implemented reasonable technical and organisational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorised access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

15\. If our privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.   
Contact   
124/125 The Strand  
GZR 1027  
Gzira, Malta  
Identification : C40939
